♪ Men, men, men, men ♪
♪ Men, men, men,
men, men, men, men. ♪
Hello.
I'm Charlie's brother Alan.
I want to thank you all
for coming.
I know this is
a very sad day
for all of us.
Speak for yourself.
Okay.
Uh, I understand that some of
you have "mixed feelings."
Um... but I think
we can all agree
that Charlie lived life
to its fullest
and-and gave it
everything he had.
Gave me herpes.
Chlamydia.
Vaginal warts.
Excuse me, this is my dead
son we're talking about.
I loved him and I'm
devastated that he's gone,
leaving me with nothing but
my memories and my regrets
and the listing for his
beautiful beachfront
Malibu getaway
with three bedrooms
and three and
a half baths
and a beautiful
panoramic ocean view.
Help yourselves to brochures
out by the coffee urn.
Thank you, Mom.
Um, anyway...
Open house is Sunday,
1:00 to 5:00.
Okay.
Um, I'd like to take a moment
to talk about my brother,
um, and his incredible love
for life.
He also loved being spanked.
While wearing
my panties.
He used my panties to make tea.
M-My point is, um, that Charlie
lived life on his own terms
and-and never apologized
for who he was.
Yeah, blah,
blah, blah.
Why can't we
see the body?
Yeah, I didn't come all this way
to spit on a closed coffin.
Okay, I understand how you feel,
but unfortunately due to the
circumstances of his passing,
the remains aren't exactly...
spit-able.
I have a question.
O-Okay.
Uh, I wasn't planning on
doing a Q and A,
uh, but go ahead.
Thank you.
Charlie owes me $38,000
for some,
let's say, pharmaceuticals.
Who do I talk to about that?
Uh, well, I think
that's something
you'll have to discuss
with the lawyers.
Yeah.
I'd rather not involve the law.
And now, uh, I thought
we'd take this moment
to hear from the person who was
with Charlie at the end.
Thank you, Alan.
Charlie Harper was
the love of my life
and a wonderful, wonderful man.
Selfish pig.
Sure, our relationship had
its ups and downs
and the occasional
restraining order.
But at the end,
we ran away together to Paris,
where he asked me to marry him.
I said yes.
And the next few days
were the happiest of my life.
Nothing could spoil it.
Not even when I came home
from shopping
and found him taking a shower
with another woman.
That's our Charlie.
But I forgave him
because I loved him
unconditionally.
So you can imagine my horror
when, the very next day,
he slipped on the Metro platform
and fell in front of
an oncoming train.
Never cross a
crazy woman.
I just want you all to know
that Charlie didn't suffer.
His body just exploded
like a balloon full of meat.
Thank you.
I'm hungry.
Anyone else hungry?
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men,
men, men ♪
♪ Ah. ♪
♪ Men. ♪
♪ Two and a Half Men 9x01 ♪
Nice to Meet You, Walden Schmidt
Original Air Date on September 19, 2010
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
♪ Men. ♪
Charlie was the best boss
I ever had.
I needed a day off,
"Sure, Berta, no problem."
I needed a couple
extra bucks,
"Sure, Berta, no problem."
All he ever asked in return
was clean sheets
and hosing the vomit off the
occasional drug-addled hooker.
What a beautiful story.
Can I count on you to keep
the house clean till I sell it?
Can I count on you
to keep paying me?
Well, there's virtually no money
in Charlie's estate,
but I'll be happy to pay you
once the house sells.
Then that's when I'll clean it.
I still don't see
why we have to sell.
I mean, he left it to me.
Obviously, he wanted me
to have it.
Can you make
the mortgage payments?
No.
Can you pay the property tax?
Not per se.
But I was kind of hoping
you'd help out.
I mean, after all, your grandson
lives here part-time.
Good job raising him.
Uh, darling, I can't afford
to maintain my house
and your house
at the same time.
But you're my mommy.
Good job raising him.
Once I sell this place,
you can come live with me.
But why would I have to?
I mean, won't I get
a lot of money from the sale?
Oh, please. Charlie had
three mortgages on this place.
Once we deduct closing costs
and escrow fees
and my commission,
you'll be lucky to break even.
Wait a minute, you're planning
to take a commission?
She doesn't work for free.
Why should I?
Don't think those silent ones
are fooling anybody.
♪ Men. ♪
Hi. I'm here
for the open house.
Of course. Come right in.
Thank you.
Three bedrooms,
three and a half baths,
60 feet of prime
Malibu oceanfront.
Wait a minute, I
know this place.
This is Charlie Harper's place,
right?
It was.
Then I can't buy it.
Uh...
What? Why?
Bad memories.
Charlie and I had this
drunken threesome with a crazy
chick right on this couch.
Sounds like a good memory.
Yeah, well,
unfortunately she passed out
and Charlie and I
kept going without her.
Bad memory.
Oh, the feng shui is great.
I mean, the place just
oozes positive energy.
It's not practical.
The commute downtown
would kill me.
Don't worry, sweetie.
Just let the universe provide.
The universe doesn't provide,
I provide.
I bust my ass 80 hours a week.
Uh-oh.
Sounds like somebody
needs to meditate.
Uh-oh.
Sounds like somebody needs
to file for divorce.
Really?
You want to play that card?
'Cause I will take you and
your uptight bourgeois family
for every penny you've got.
Bye-bye!
What a fun couple.
♪ Men. ♪
Sorry, the open
house is over.
I got a package
for Alan Harper.
Oh, uh, that's me.
Sign here.
Ooh, how exciting.
Wonder what it is.
It's from a crematorium,
so that kind of
narrows it down.
That's, uh,
that's my brother.
Berta,
Charlie's here!
Thank you.
Enjoy.
Well...
here we are, buddy.
Just like old times, huh?
I'm talking and you're
in a bottle ignoring me.
I, uh, I wanted to tell you,
uh, that I loved you,
and I will miss you,
and I will always be grateful
for you taking Jake and me in,
letting us live here
all these years.
So, now the question is...
what do we do with you?
I know what you said
you wanted, but...
I really don't think
Pamela Anderson will agree
to swallow your ashes.
Um, I-I could take you with me
to live at Mom's,
but that's how
horror movies start.
Hey.
Maybe I could sprinkle you
on the beach.
I mean, it's simple,
it's dignified,
and pretty girls
covered with oil
will be sitting on you all day.
Kind of like your life.
Except for the dignified part.
All right.
Well...
I guess now is
as good a time as any.
I ain't cleaning him up.
♪ Men. ♪
Can I use your phone?
Sure.
I guess.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
I was just trying
to drown myself.
Wait, you-you tried
to commit suicide?
Yeah. But I had no idea that
the water would be that cold.
Suppose I could've
worn a wet suit,
but who tries to commit suicide
in a wet suit, right?
That phone right there?
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Thank you.
Uh, you got a towel?
Oh, sure.
Thanks.
Hi. It's me.
I want you to know that I just
flung myself in the ocean
'cause I can't live without you.
No, I'm not calling you
from the ocean.
Because it was cold.
I don't...
I'm in some guy's house.
Um, Alan Harper.
I am in Alan
Harper's house.
How about it?
Will you take me back?
Are you sure?
You heard what I said
about the ocean, right?
Okay, fine.
I'll stop bothering you.
But I want you to know that I
will love you forever and ever.
Really?
That bothers you?
Okay. Bye.
You got a wet suit?
Oh, come on.
It... it can't be that bad.
It could be.
You don't know.
No, no, I do.
Come on. Come on.
Sit down. Sit down.
Listen.
I have been
where you are--
uh, rejected,
friendless, broke.
I'm not broke.
I'm worth, like,
a billion dollars.
Beg pardon?
1.3 is what her lawyer says,
but I would give up every penny
if she would take me back.
No, no, no.
You don't want to do that.
Uh... I think you can find a lot
of girls for way less money.
I don't want other girls.
I want Bridget.
Right. Right.
Um, just to clarify, um,
did you say "billion"
with a "buh?"
Listen, trust me.
Money does not
buy happiness.
I wouldn't know.
I've never had either.
Come on.
You're doing all right.
You're living in
a beach house in Malibu.
I have to sell it.
And it's not even mine;
it's his.
His?
That's my dead brother.
Oh.
I'm sorry I made you spill him.
That's okay. That's okay.
I'll DustBust him later.
You know what?
I'll get out of your way.
Thank you for letting me
use your phone.
Wait, hang on.
You sure you're okay?
Yeah. I'm just going to go back
to my hotel room
and update my Facebook status
to "not dead yet."
Wait, wait, wait. I...
I just went to one funeral.
I-I don't want to be involved
in another one.
Why don't you and I go out
and have a drink and talk?
About what?
Oh, I don't know.
The weather, politics.
Why somebody would want
to kill themselves
when they have
a billion freaking dollars.
Come on.
We'll, uh, put your clothes
in the dryer.
All right.
Oh, by the way...
I'm Walden.
Walden Schmidt.
Well, it's nice to meet
you, Walden Schmidt.
Oh. Oh, sure. I suppose
there's no reason
you can't undress right
here in the living room.
Oh, Skivvies coming off, too.
Okay. Okay, well, uh,
no body issues.
Lucky you. That's...
You're a good guy,
Alan Harper.
Oh, and he's a
hugger as well.
Okeydokey.
I'll be right back.
$1.3 billion,
and he's hung like an elephant.
♪ Men. ♪
Uh, I will have
an appletini.
Uh, and, um...?
Oh, uh, ginger
ale, please.
Really?
Fresh off
a suicide attempt,
and you're ordering
a ginger ale?
Yeah. I don't like
the taste of alcohol.
Nobody likes
We like the effects
of alcohol.
How it makes you feel tall,
good-looking and smart.
I am tall, good-looking
and smart.
Give him an appletini.
So, just out of curiosity,
how does someone get
to be worth so much money?
Oh, it's pretty
simple, really.
You ever hear of
Blungogo.com?
No.
And you never will,
because Microsoft
bought it from me
for $1.3 billion, and
then they bundled it
with their iPod
killer, the Zune.
Really?
I don't think it
came with my Zune.
You bought a Zune?
I had a coupon.
Cheers?
Oh. Cheers.
So, don't take this
the wrong way,
but I can't get the image
of your penis out of my mind.
Thank you.
That's very sweet.
♪ Men. ♪
You don't understand.
Bridget was my
high school sweetheart.
She was the love
of my life.
So why'd she leave you?
She catch you
with another woman?
- No.
- Sex no good?
No, it was great.
Are you sure?
'Cause sometimes they'll
tell you it's good,
and then you
find out later
they hated
the very touch of you.
Happened to a guy I know.
Well, she said that I was
emotionally immature.
You mean like
threatening suicide
unless she
takes you back?
That is not immature;
that's romantic.
Shut up.
Well, regardless, I-I know
what you're going through.
I mean, I married
my college sweetheart,
and when she divorced me,
I was devastated.
Why did she leave you?
Not a clue.
She's a crazy bitch.
The point is,
when life serves you
ball breakers
who rip your heart out,
you have to make...
ball breaker-ade.
Bridget never
broke my balls.
If anything,
she treated them
with tenderness
and respect.
Okay. Okay,
just for tonight,
will you... will you
forget about Bridget
and-and just try
to meet somebody new?
Like who?
I don't know.
How about...
how about her?
Really?
What would I say?
Uh, well, I would not lead
with the testicle anecdote.
Just... just say hi.
Okay.
Hi.
- I'm Walden.
- Kelly.
So, Kelly...
My... wife dumped me,
and I want to die.
Oh, you poor baby.
I love her so much.
I... I don't...
Whew! I don't know...
if I can ever
love anyone
the way
that I love her.
That's the most beautiful thing
that I've ever heard.
Oh, it'll be okay.
Oh, God, I miss my wife!
♪ Men. ♪
Here is where I live.
Oh.
Nice.
Just me and my broken heart.
Alan, I... I think
I should go back to my hotel.
Are you nuts?
We're doing great.
This crap about loving
our exes is gold.
My brother
would be so proud.
What, the dude in
the DustBuster?
Yeah.
Ah. Uh, ladies, uh,
who's up for a libation?
- A what?
- Huh?
A... a drink-- alcohol.
- Sure.
- Great.
Oh. Be right back.
What's upstairs?
I don't know.
Probably a bedroom.
Why don't we
go find out?
Uh... okay.
Hey, shouldn't we tell Alan
where we're going?
No.
Who's ready for margaritas?
Wow!
One at a time, ladies!
One at a time.
Well, this is depressingly
familiar.
Shut up.
♪ Men. ♪
Morning.
Oh, good golly.
Oh, uh, I'm Walden.
I'm impressed.
Oh. Alan.
Guess what.
I had sex with two girls
last night.
Great. Um, I masturbated
and cried myself to sleep.
I like my night better.
Oh, hey.
I dig your house,
so I'm going to buy it, okay?
Oh, okay.
Thanks.
You're the best.
Oh... ah.
Whoa.
Um, this is Walden.
He's going to
buy the house.
Welcome
to my humble abode.
I like him.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==